Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor/Executive Vice President (Borowitz) RG.6.0.7
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative
  - Lists, President/Chancellor Luncheons: Faculty and Administrators, Feb 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lists, President/Chancellor Luncheons: Faculty and Administrators, Arrangements, May 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lists, Trustees, Aug 1970-Aug 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Management Study Group, Sep 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Schedules, Misc, Sep 1972-Sep 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, Nov 1973-May 1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Museum Studies, Study Group on, Sep 1974-Dec 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Office Matters, Misc, Feb 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Office Services, Mail, Sep 1967-Feb 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Organization, University, Jan 1973-Mar 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224948 5
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York (PINY), Misc, Mar 1974-Jan 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - President, Drafts for, Aug 1973-Aug 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - President, Investiture (Sawhill), Nov 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - President, Nixon Task Force on Higher Education (Hester), Oct 1970-Nov1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - President, Reports for, Aug 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - President, Reports to University Community (Hester), Sep 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - President, Reports to University Community (Sawhill), Aug 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - President, Reports to University Community (Sawhill), Jul 1975-Sep 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - President, Speeches (Hester), Feb 1970-Oct 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - President, Speeches (Sawhill), Nov 1975-May 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - President, Strategy Meetings with (Hester), May 1974-Sep 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Citations; Distinguished Service Awards, Apr 1975-Sep 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reports, Misc, Sexton Class Report on Washington Square Park, May 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Schweitzer Chair, Jun 1975-Sep 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224949 3
  - Sponsored Programs (see also Fed. Relations), Sep 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Programs (see also Fed. Relations), Sep 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Sep 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Sep 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Sep 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, Mar 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs, Senate Report on, Apr 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Travel Schedule (Borowitz), Dec 1972-Jan 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - United Fund, Oct 1973-Nov 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - University Functions, May 1974-Dec 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - University Calendar, Holiday & Vacation, Sep 1972-May 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Work & Development Plans, President & Chancellor, Jul 1975-Oct 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Subseries I: Correspondence
    Materials in this sub-series include chronological correspondence files, including those that were created during the Chancellorship of Allan M. Cartter during the period beginning April 1971 and overlapping with Borowitz correspondence files of May 1972. These materials date between 1972 and 1977.
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Apr 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224950 1
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Mar 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Feb 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Dec 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Nov 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Oct 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Sep 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Aug 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jul 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jun 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, May 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Apr 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Mar 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Feb 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Dec 1975 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Nov 1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Oct 1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Sep 1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Aug 1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jul 1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jun 1975 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, May 1975 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Apr 1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Mar 1975 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Feb 1975 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Dec 1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Nov 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Oct 1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Sep 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Aug 1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jul 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224951 9
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jun 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Apr 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Mar 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Feb 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Dec 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Nov 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Oct 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Sep 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Aug 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jul 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jun 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, May 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Apr 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Mar 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Feb 1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Dec 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Nov 1972 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Oct 1972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Sep 1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Aug 1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jul 1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Chron File, Jun 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter & S Borowitz, May 1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Apr 1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Mar 1972 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Feb 1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Jan 1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Dec 1971 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Nov 1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Oct 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224952 7
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Sep 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Chron File: AM Cartter, Apr 1971-Aug 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Condolence Letters, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Invitations, Jan 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Invitations, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Invitations, Jan 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Invitations, May 1973-Dec 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Letters Answered for the President, May 1972-Feb 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Mar 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Feb 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jan 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Dec 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Nov 1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Oct 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Sep 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jun 1976 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Mar 1976 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Feb 1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jan 1976 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Dec 1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Nov 1975 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Oct 1975 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Sep 1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Aug 1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jul 1975 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jun 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224953 5
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, May 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Apr 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Mar 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Feb 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jan 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Dec 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Nov 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Oct 1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Sep 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Aug 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jul 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jun 1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, May 1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Apr 1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Mar 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Feb 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jan 1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Dec 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Nov 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Oct 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Sep 1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Aug 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jul 1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jun 1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, May 1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Apr 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Mar 1973 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jan 1973-Mar 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log, Jun 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log (from President's Office), Jun 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log (from President's Office), May 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Mail Log Referrals (Outgoing Mail), Jun 1972-May 1973 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Log Material: AM Cartter, Jan 1972-May 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224954 3
    - Correspondence, Log Material: AM Cartter, Oct 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Log Material: AM Cartter, Jul 1971-Sep 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Manual & Guides, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Misc, Jan 1977-Jun 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Misc (A-G), 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Misc (H-R), 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Misc (S-Z), 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Office Procedures & Sample Formats, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Personal Recommendations (A-H), Jul 1970-Jun 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Personal Recommendations (K-Z), Jul 1970-Jun 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Jul 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224955 0
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Jun 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Mar 1976-May 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Dec 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Sep 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Apr 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, President's Office, Jan 1972-Dec 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Series II: Associations
  This series of 1.66 linear feet reflects a universe of external organizations concerned with higher education matters, both on the national and on the local scene, and memberships held and declined by the University. This series' contents offer insights into the University's interests and roles in that wider world. A set of Higher Education and National Affairs newsletters, 3/74-2/76, 3/77-4/77, published by the American Council on Education (ACE), provides an overview of the national context in which the higher education community was then functioning.
  Material contained in Box 19, folder 1, makes manifest that limitations on extramural involvements that might otherwise have been welcome were driven by internal financial concerns, with oversight of unit and school decisions at the executive level. Matters concerned with the University and its accreditation agency, the Middle States Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, Commission on Higher Education, are located in Box 20, folders 7-8, including the Middle States Association Report on its visit to the University 11/18-21/73.
  Memberships in Washington, D.C.-based higher education associations of importance to university interests were in the American Council on Education (ACE), Box 19, folders 5-8 and the Association of American Universities (AAU), Box 19, folders 12-15. Further information, often detailing NYU interests, appears in Box 6, folders 8-12.
  At the state level, relevant memberships were in the Association of Colleges & Universities of the State of New York (ACUNY), Box 19, folder 16, and most actively in the ACUNY subset Commission on Independent Colleges & Universities (CICU), Box 19, folder 17 and Box 20, folders 1-2. Additional materials reflecting particular university interests at the state level can be found in Box 7, folders 11-14, and Box 8, folders 1-3.
  Records of membership in two discipline focused associations, both of which required institutional commitments at the executive level, and which were affected by the University's financial problems, are located in Box 21, folders 1-2, the University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, and in Box 22, folders 4-7, the New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges and Universities, Inc.
  - Correspondence, Memberships and Subscriptions, Oct 1971-Mar 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224956 8
  - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE), Sep 1971-Mar 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), Mar 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), Nov 1971-Jul 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), Jul 1974-Sep 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), Nov 1973-May 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), Sep 1973-Oct 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), Dec 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Higher Education & National Affairs (ACE) Newsletter, Mar 1974-Feb 1976, Mar 1977-Apr 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Association of American Colleges (AAC), Dec 1973-Dec 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Association of American Colleges (AAC), Sep 1972-Aug 1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), Sep 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), Sep 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Association of American Universities(AAU), Jan 1974-Aug 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), Jun 1972-Oct 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Association of Colleges & Universities of the State of NY (ACUNY), May 1971-Jul 1975 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - ACUNY/Commission on Independent Colleges & Universities(CICU), Oct 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - ACUNY/Commission on Independent Colleges & Universities (CICU), Oct 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224957 6
  - ACUNY/Commission on Independent Colleges & Universities (CICU), May 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - College Entrance Exam Board (CEEB), Apr 1972-Jun 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, College Level Examination Program (CLEP), 1974-Jan 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars (CIES), Nov 1973-Sep 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - International Research & Exchanges Board (IREX), Jan 1973-Sep 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, Commission on Higher Education & Other, Sep 1973-May 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, Commission on Higher Education & Other, Dec 1971-Mar 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Associations, Misc (A - American Association for the Advancement of Science), undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Associations, Misc (American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies - B), undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Associations, Misc (C-I), undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Associations, Misc (N-Y), undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), Jul 1973-Feb 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Correspondence, Jan 1974-Jan 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224958 4
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Correspondence, Dec 1972-Dec 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Minutes, Oct 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Minutes, Nov 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Minutes, Jan 1973-Oct 1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Reports, Newsletters, Announcements, Nov 1972-Feb 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research(NCAR/UCAR), Reports, Annual Report 1975 An Institutional History, 1960-1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Reports, Newsletters, Announcements, Annual Report of Members for 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224959 2
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research(NCAR/UCAR), Reports, Newsletters, Announcements, Annual Report of Members for 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research/University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (NCAR/UCAR), Reports, Newsletters, Announcements, Annual Report of Members for 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges & Universities, Inc., Mar 1975-Sep 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges & Universities, Inc., Jan 1974-Oct 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges & Universities, Inc., Feb 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges & Universities, Inc., May 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, Beta Chapter, Apr 1973-Feb 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Series III: Development
  This series comprises 1.25 linear feet and is structured to reflect several major aspects of the portfolio of the Senior Vice President for External Affairs, namely: Alumni Affairs; the Bicentennial Committee; Development, including donor solicitation and acknowledgment correspondence and foundation relations; the NYU Press; and the Office of the Senior Vice President.
  Notable materials include meeting minutes of the NYU Committee on the (United States) Bicentennial, Box 23, folders 3-4, a draft development campaign mission statement, "A View of Our Responsibilities and Our Opportunities," 3/7/73, Box 23, folder 5, NYU's proposal to the Ford Foundation for an Emergency Fund Grant to support reorganization and retrenchment programs, 7/5/72, and its undated final narrative report, 11/75? Box 24, folders 2-3, Borowitz on the role of a university press, 11/9/76, Box 25, folders 1,4, NYU Press Statement of Purpose, 3/19/76, Box 25, folder 4.
  - Alumni Affairs, Misc, Aug 1971-Jul 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224960 0
  - Alumni Affairs, New York University Club, Sep 1972-Mar 1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bicentennial Committee, Sep 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bicentennial Committee, May 1974-Jun 1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Development Campaign, Mar 1973-Nov 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (A-J), Jan 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (K-Y), Jan 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (B-W), Jul 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (A-J), Feb 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (K-Z), Feb 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters (A-Y), Jul 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Donor Acknowledgment Letters, Jun 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Corporation, Feb 1971-Feb 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, Oct 1972-Jun 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Danforth Foundation, Mar 1973-Apr 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Esso, Exxon Education Foundation, Oct 1971-Sep 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ford Foundation, Feb 1974-May 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224961 8
  - Ford Foundation, Jul 1970-Nov 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, Apr 1973-Mar 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Kevorkian Fund, Sep 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, Sep 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sloan Foundation, Jun 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fund Raising, Bequests & Estates, Apr 1973-Apr 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fund Raising, Correspondence, Jan 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Fund Raising, Correspondence, Jan 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Fund Raising, Correspondence, Oct 1967-Dec 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raising, Grants and Gifts, Feb 1973-Nov 1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Fund Raising, Grants and Gifts, Jan 1971-Dec 1972 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fund Raising Policy Statement and Schedule, May 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Fund Raising, Proposals, Apr 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Fund Raising, Proposals, Feb 1974-Feb 1976 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Fund Raising, Proposals, Dec 1973-Jan 1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - NYU Press, Audits, Oct 1971-Oct 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - NYU Press, Director, Sep 1976-Jun 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224962 6